Thanks for looking.
Hello! This time I'll be talking with Saori Onoda from Tsubaki Factory and Nanami Kubota from Ocha no Oma!
We'll be showing you the latest news from the two of them, so please bear with us until the end.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Yes, actually, we were together this time as MCs in the preliminary survey for the Halo! I wrote your name in the questionnaire in advance of the event.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for allowing me to speak.
By the way, why did you want to be an MC with us?
We have the same pink color and character, I guess you could call it.
I don't call myself that.
It's not self-proclaimed.
They are two cute girls, and they are so cute and sparkling on the screen, so I thought I'd like to be an MC with them someday.
I'm so happy.
I'm very happy.
We're so cute!
I think it's the best thing to MC with two cute girls, so I hope you enjoy it.
We've just finished Hina Fest 2024 and Carbon Neutral 2024x Satoyama Umi Movement.
This recording is before the event, so we are still in the process of predicting what kind of event it will be, but what do you hope it will be like?
What do you want the event to be like?
The tea horses didn't win any prizes in the raffle last year.
That's unusual, isn't it?
Last year we were very sad about that.
But this year, half of them won.
That's a lot of people suddenly won.
I'm glad.
Kubota won't be performing this year, but I'll be cheering for everyone and hope they all make it.
I hope you all have a great time!
And the Tea Horse Tour will be starting soon!
Yay!
And when is Tea Horse live?
Yes, the Tea Horse Live Tour 2024 will start on April 7th in Osaka, Japan.
Yes, I think there will be more songs from the album this time compared to last time.
I hope you can see the more powerful Ochanoma this time.
I'm also very interested in the album of Tea Horse.
There are songs that the three of us sing together, right?
That's right.
So I thought it would be nice if I could have a chance to see it.
I thought it was wonderful, and I wish I had a chance to do it.
That's right.
That's why I thought it was so wonderful, and I wish I had the chance to do something about it.
Thank you very much.
Tsubaki Factory, to which I belong, is going to hold a concert tour in spring 2024.
Come Everybody" will start on the 3rd of May in Kanagawa prefecture!
Let's see, Tsubaki Factory has 3 new members and 5 new members in the group.
Kisara Niinuma will be graduating, so this will be the last tour with the current Tsubaki Factory.
We will only be able to tour 3 places.
I feel so sad.
I'm feeling very sad, but I'm also very determined to put my heart into these three places, so we're all going to work together as one and do our best.
Now then, please take a look at this video.
Here you go!
Way to go!
I wanna see you dance
Diamond, diamond, diamond you
Let's shake together
Let me burn up, I'll make sure I do Diamond, diamond, diamond you
Let's dance, dance, dance I do diamond
Be more like you
End save, it's a sparkle
Just say your name
You're the next one to reach me
Woo woo
Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow
Hey!
Where did you come from, who recognized you
I met you in the rough and tumble
I thought my tears would flow if they were closed inside my chest
It would be so much easier if I let it go longer
I don't want to get dirty
Made Up Time also burns up, extreme kuwarikatsu
Burn and shine, I was lost
I could cry without forgetting, it's only in the past
Let's dance together
Whatever rags and tatters dance, no matter who you are
High to Gaea, empty nights
High to Gaia, too
I want to cry more for this star, more for the future
And all of you
Woo woo woo
I'm gonna burn up, I'm gonna burn up, I'm gonna burn up, I'm gonna burn up
High to Gaia, too
Let's dance, let's dance
♪ And the high to Gaia
Be more you, don't hold back, shine
Just be yourself
The light will run out, but it will reach you
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Which book? Which book?
I'll try to put it into words
Courage. Such loneliness.
It's the hardest thing I've ever had to do
Cause you're not the only one
A little map We are all
What two people are crying
I don't care if it shakes or overflows
It was better to go
Let's say together
Cause you're not the only one
Hey!
Catway, black roll, sole, mezzer
Hey! Now the future I don't want it to sparkle
TV Randy Runner
Hey!
Wow!
♪ Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa
Let's shake together
I don't care what kind of a wreck you are
I do diamond
Even on the saddest of nights
I want to make it a mirror mirror through my heart
Mirror ball
Even if the buzz-boom-boom ball burns out
I do diamond
Let's dance, let's dance
Just like you
I do diamond
I want to be inspired
I want to bring out your uniqueness
I can shine without restraint
Just set it up, please
I love you, this night
Diamond, diamond, diamond you
Let's shine together
Yay!
I'm sure you'll be fine as usual
Saori Onoda of Tsubaki Factory and Nanami Kubota of Ocha-no-Ma
and Nanami Kubota of Ocha-no-Ma, the tea factory, present "Halo! stay!
From here, we'd like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so let's answer them without thinking too much and at a quick pace.
First of all, I'd like to ask you a question already.
Nanami, who loves manga, what is your latest favorite work?
Hot Love Prince, My Brother Likes You!
What is the first thing that comes to your mind when you hear the word "Gahabi"?
Chocolate!
This weekend, the tour will start with more than twice as many performances as before.
What are you consciously working on for the long tour?
Taking care of my physical condition.
What is your favorite part of your makeup?
Blush.
If you were to compare yourself to an animal, what would it be?
A rabbit.
Wow! So cute!
Thank you.
I thought it was really cute, and I thought all the answers were really cute.
I just thought it was really cute and I thought all the answers were really cute.
I wanted to ask you a few questions.
When I heard the word "reward", the first thing that came to my mind was
I gave him chocolates.
Do you like sweets?
I love sweets.
I have a personality that when I get into something, I eat it all the time.
I see.
Recently, I've been addicted to chocolate.
On days when I work hard, I eat a big bag of chocolates in one day.
That's amazing.
You can eat it all?
I'll eat it all.
She's so cute, but she eats it all.
I just thought of that now.
Also, this is a question I thought of.
What is your favorite part of makeup?
She's so cute.
I was wondering if you have any particular points of interest in makeup.
I was just wondering.
I love blush.
I think girls with reddish-pink cheeks are cute.
I think it's cute when they have cheeks like that.
So I put a lot of blush on my cheeks.
I put a lot of blush on my cheeks.
I put a lot of blush on my cheeks to make them look a bit cheeky.
Then I'd like to put blush on my cheeks, too.
We'll have more questions for Ms. Onoda after the VTR.
Hello! Sta!
Getchu!
Ochanomama's first album Channel 1 is now on sale!
Halo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask Ms. Onoda a question.
Yes, Onoda-san, the leader of the cute gang!
What is the most recent incident in which you were overflowing with cuteness?
Yes, a friend took a picture of me and it was too cute.
Yes, sir.
Next week, Tsubaki Factory Concert Tour 2023 Autumn, Atara yo!
Riko Yamagishi Yume Kishimoto's graduation special "Dawn" video work will be released!
What do you want people to see again and again?
Riko Yume's salon
Yes, and Ms. Onoda, who said in a magazine interview last year that she wanted to do her best in singing.
What have you been working on for this in the past year?
Rhythm practice.
Onoda-san, you have a lot of facial expressions when you perform live.
Yes, I do.
You're so cute!
Yes, and last month you held a live performance to celebrate the 7th anniversary of your major label debut.
Looking back on the anniversary live, please say a few words.
My ears are happy!
Happy ears!
Thank you so much!
I was thinking of Onoda-san, who has a lot of facial expressions during the live performance, and that's the question I was trying to answer.
Thank you very much.
I love Onoda-san's facial expressions so much.
This is my favorite one.
Yes.
This is the cutest face I've ever seen.
Is it? I make my cutest face.
This is me.
That's the image I have of you.
You're right, it's not the right pose, but...
Yes, I do.
I'm going to continue to show off my cuteness.
And what I want you to see at this graduation concert of Riko Yamagishi and Yumeno Kishimoto will be their solos.
Yes, that's right.
When I saw Riko and Yume singing alone at the end of encore, it was such a wonderful space that I was moved to tears.
People who graduate really become more beautiful.
I think it's a precious video to see them at their most beautiful, so please watch it a lot.
I hope you will watch the video as much as possible. Stay tuned for the rest of the show!
Thank you for watching!
This is Natsuyaki Kimiyabi.
Here we go!
Hello Kitchen!
This time we have a member here with us.
This is Sumire Tashiro from Ocha-no-Uma.
Pleased to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Tashiro.
Nice to meet you.
Now let's see what we're going to make this time.
Today's dish is Wagyu Beef Tagliata
Balsamic Sauce
So here are the ingredients
What is tagliata?
Tagliata is an Italian dish.
Italian cuisine means "thinly sliced".
Thinly sliced
like roast beef.
It's a rather small piece of meat.
Thinly sliced into thin strips.
Scatter it on top of the salad.
That's how it's cooked.
Sounds delicious.
Do you usually cook?
I don't cook these days.
I used to cook at home when I was little.
I'm remembering that today.
I would like to be able to improve even more.
Yes, I'll try my best.
Then, let's do our best.
I look forward to working with you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
What shall we do first? Wagyu beef dagliata, that's what we'll call it.
We can't start without meat, so I've prepared this today.
Wagyu beef fillet.
It's going to be a luxury. I put salt on the meat for the first time.
You can't find meat this size in this condition.
I don't think you can find meat this size in this condition.
What difference does it make?
Just a pinch of salt will bring out the moisture.
I'll let it sit for 10 to 15 minutes.
I'll let it rest for 10 to 15 minutes, so watch it later.
Then we'll go on to the potatoes.
Potatoes.
About 100 grams. I brought some new potatoes.
Delicious ones.
Wash them with your hands. It's a lot of fun.
It's been a while. Cooking itself is fun.
Cooking itself is fun! It'll be useful in the future!
Let's put them in and let them soak in water for a bit.
It's very starchy, so by soaking it...
Soak it in water, so it won't stick to the pan when you bake it.
It won't stick together.
On the other hand, there are times when you want them to stick together.
I see. So you don't soak them in that kind of water?
No, I don't.
I put it in the microwave.
I put it in the microwave, but I burn it flat, and close the mouth a little.
Put it in the microwave like this, and let it rest for a minute.
Wow, it looks hot, but it's really soft.
I can eat it.
I want to brown it, but I'm going to put a little oil in it, but it might pop because of the moisture.
I'd like to brown them, but I'd like to put a little oil in them.
So that the noodles are all set in the pan.
I'm sure you don't want to cut it and cook it here.
It's also very tasty.
If there's not enough oil, it turns black instead of golden brown, so oil is very important.
It's perfect. It's perfect.
It's so beautifully browned, and a little bit of salt here and there.
It's already delicious.
It's hot, it's hot, it's hot. Are you okay? - I'm fine.
It's so good! It's so good! It's so sweet!
It's good. It's going to be even better.
It will taste even better.
Yes, it will.
Now let's move on to making the sauce.
Balsamic vinegar is a black Italian vinegar.
This is a special sauce that you can make with just these three ingredients.
It looks delicious, it's similar in color... yes, different country, different taste, totally different...
Yes, and here's the point of Miyabi vinegar... you boil it down to make it thicker.
Yes, that's right, you have to boil it down.
It tastes almost like water.
I'd like to ask you a few questions while the sauce is simmering.
Is there anything you're into right now, or is there something you're particular about?
Yes, I'm really into photography right now.
I bought a digital camera, not a cell phone
I bought a digital camera, not a smartphone, but an old digital camera.
How do you feel about the pictures you take? The pictures you take are totally different from the pictures you take with your phone.
I'm very happy when I post them on my blog and people respond to them.
I take pictures of people.
Landscape?
I take landscapes, and I also take portraits of people, but I think it's the members who are the most important.
When I go on tour, I take pictures of everyone as a memory of the various places we go.
I also take pictures of myself that are not in the picture.
But I like taking pictures. I prefer to take pictures of people rather than being photographed.
So I take pictures of the members.
And while I'm on the road, they look like this.
They're all stuck together like this.
It's amazing!
It's already turned to mush.
So here's a teaspoon of honey.
One teaspoon, about 10 grams.
When you put the honey in, turn off the heat.
It's better if it's already off.
It looks like a delicious sauce.
It's like a sauce. I'm going to taste it with a spoon over there.
It's delicious.
I thought it might have a strong vinegar taste, but it doesn't.
It's not sour.
All the sourness just flew away, so...
I added some more honey at the end.
Honey honey honey
It's delicious.
It's a little mellow.
I'm going to keep it for now.
That's all for now.
Next time, I'll finish cooking the meat and so on.
I'd like to do my best to serve it properly.
Let's do our best and look forward to seeing you next time!
Please look forward to the next installment.
I'm really looking forward to the next installment.
I'm looking forward to it!
Speaking of cooking, Mao Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory
of Tsubaki Factory gave handmade cookies as a gift to the members.
She told us that she made the cookies with Rikako Sasaki of Angelem.
She talked about them a lot and thought they looked delicious, so she gave them to me as a gift.
She gave them to me as a gift when she thought they looked delicious.
I thought it was so cute that she gave me a message saying she loved Saori.
I thought how cute she was and I realized how nice Mao Akiyama is.
Above all, the cookies were so delicious!
There were not only one kind of cookie, but there were many kinds of cookies, like chocolate flavor and plain cookies.
That's why I thought she was so dexterous.
I want to eat Mao Akiyama's homemade cookies again!
Actually, there is a member of Ocha-no-Ma who is into cooking these days.
Rocco Tsutsui is one of them.
Lately, she's been making things like mentaiko (salted cod roe) bread and chocolate bread.
and put them in a bag for the members.
She told us to eat them like this.
It was so delicious!
I wish I could cook and deliver them to the members someday.
What is your mentaiko salt bread like?
You know that salted bread?
Yes, the salted bread... in the shape of a salt bun.
It's got mentaiko (cod roe) in the middle.
Looks delicious!
It's really fluffy.
It's fluffy?
Wow, that's amazing.
It's really good.
Bread takes so much time to make.
It's wonderful that you make bread while you're working.
You really have a lot of feminine charm.
I admire that.
Haloste
Next is the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart.
Hello Project has a lot of great lyrics.
We asked ourselves, "What lyrics or phrases can make us feel positive? We've been thinking of lyrics and phrases that make us feel positive.
Do you have any?
Yes, I'm going to write a song called "Good Luck's Chestburst" by Ocha-no-Mama.
In the B melody of the song, there is a lyric that says, "If you just wait, chances will easily pass you by.
I may look like this, but I'm a shy person.
I'm the type of person who wonders if it's okay to be forward or not.
That's right.
So there are times when I regret not doing it.
So these lyrics make me feel that if I don't go out in front, I won't get a chance.
I love these lyrics because they make me want to work harder.
It's so nice, isn't it, when you're performing?
Whether I'm singing or not
Even when I'm singing, even when I'm looking at the members...
the lyrics really move me and make me want to work harder.
Even during a live performance.
I want you to feel the lyrics
I hope you can feel the lyrics, and we want to have fun too.
I, Saori Onoda
From the new album released on February 21
I would like to dream about the song "Power Flower, Now is the time to be united" from the new album released on Feb. 21.
The lyrics of the chorus, "The dream I want to make bloom all over the world, I can't make it come true alone..."
I love the lyrics "I can't make it happen alone.
I love it so much.
I can't make it come true on my own" is part of the song.
It is so true.
The title of the song also has the message of "now is the time to be united as one".
Tsubaki Factory is very forward thinking.
Tsubaki Factory has a strong spirit of "move forward".
Now is the time for us to come together as one and move forward with the current Tsubaki Factory.
I thought the lyrics were filled with this feeling.
I was very encouraged when I saw the lyrics.
And when I actually sing the part, I feel it more
I think I feel it more when I sing the part.
Now, please watch the VTR.
Here it is!
Presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we will present lyrics from FaroProject's songs that have touched our hearts, and talk about their charms.
I hope you, the viewers of "FARO STE", will also understand the charm of the songs.
This week, I, Takashi Kitagawa, will be presenting.
Let's go.
Here it is.
Don't compare, don't be overshadowed, people are people, don't be jealous, only you can be special.
This is the song "Hey Unf Unfair" by Morning Musume。 19's "Hey Unfair Baby",
This "Hey Unfair Baby" was the first song recorded by the 15th term.
It means a lot to me that I was given these lyrics at that time,
I have a tendency to think negatively,
I tend to compare myself with others, or get depressed because I envy others,
I tend to compare myself with others, envy others, and get depressed, but at times like that, this lyric reminds me of three things,
I think that people are just people, and that it's okay to be special,
I am slow to learn how to dance, I am not good at remembering lyrics, and so on,
I think I am clumsy at dancing,
I think I'm clumsy at dancing, but I'm trying to love myself for that,
This song makes me feel the troubles again.
Wow.
I don't know how to say it, but the lyrics of this song are very energizing.
The choreography is the same,
I have never performed it before,
I have never performed it, but I would love to perform it at festivals and so on,
I think it would give the song courage,
I really thought about this song.
The tune of the song is quite guitar-oriented, strong, and bright,
I would certainly like to play it at festivals,
I would certainly like to perform it.
I have never performed it, and I have only seen the video,
But there was a time when this song cheered me up,
I could really relate to it.
I really want to do it someday.
I would love to do it.
I really want to do it.
Please pay attention to the lyrics when you do.
Yes, I will.
So, that's all for now, Navy and the lyrics presentation.
Please look forward to the next installment.
Saori Onoda of Tsubaki Factory and Nanami Kubota of Ocha-no-Oma will be presenting "Halo! station.
On March 10, Tsubaki Factory's major debut 7th anniversary live "REALIZE" was held.
We performed with a live band for this live, and we also performed with a live band for the 6th anniversary live,
I was very happy to be able to perform with a live band again this year.
I wanted to create a live performance that could only be done with a live band,
We wanted to create a live show that could only be performed by a live band, so we decided to have an acoustic version, or a version that could only be heard at this live performance,
One of the challenges for this year's concert was to perform with a microphone stand for the first time among the current members,
I was very excited to see them perform with a microphone stand for the first time, which is something you don't see often in idol performances,
It was the first time for many of us to do something like that,
We all practiced how to use it and how to use it together, and tried to dress up a little,
I think it's a live performance that everyone thought up together.
From Tsubaki Factory's 7th anniversary live "REALIZE," we present "STAY FREE & STAY TUNED.
This one is from the new album "3rd MOMENT," which was released on February 21,
This is a song from our new album, 3rd Moment, which was released on February 21,
This song was included in the 3rd moment of the new album released on February 21,
We performed it for the first time on March 10.
We were finally able to perform it for the first time,
We had been wondering when we would be able to perform it, since we had been working on the dance choreography,
I was very happy to finally perform it for the first time,
This song is a song that you can sing along with your fans,
It's amazing, when you hear the sound, you can hear a little "ooh-oh-oh" sound that you can sing along with.
It's amazing, when you listen to the sound, you can hear a little sound that you can sing "ooh-oh-oh".
So if you get the album,
I mean, you kind of check your part a little bit in the last chorus part,
It's like the fans are checking it with me,
So I would like to practice and create this song together,
I wrote on social networking sites that I wanted the song to be sung.
So I guess everyone could have guessed that,
So I think everyone could have predicted the performance,
So I actually sang "REALIZE" with them,
I actually sang with them on this "REALIZE",
I was able to anticipate what everyone was going to do, and I was able to perform after a little bit of anticipation,
I actually sang with them in this "REALIZE",
Some people really sang along,
Chorus?
We were able to perform together,
I was able to perform with everyone,
I still have the impression that it was a lot of fun.
The fans really started from the very first performance,
The fans were always calling out in unison from the very first performance,
Really? It's amazing, isn't it?
It was really amazing.
It's refreshing to see them united together,
It's refreshing to see them unite as one,
It makes us feel like we have to work even harder.
I hope we can continue to have fun together.
Please take a look.
by H.
We have to be more aggressive.
If you don't give up, you'll keep going, and you'll find that you're getting tighter and tighter.
I realize I've come a long way.
To achieve one thing, we must turn the corner
Meeting and parting again and again, I feel the gratitude that wells up in me
I know it's too uneven
But that's the charm of it, that's rather the cuchillado stone
Gusayl Safely I feel like I shouldn't be satisfied
Together we'll set out for a world yet to be seen Step by step, embracing the things that must not be changed
Let's keep changing
I'm not the one who did it with more sevens
I've been there and done that, but even that's just a passing rock
No matter how big our mistakes or our scars
If we're too perfect, it'll be fun.
Make room, show your weakness, follow each other
Stand free on the journey that takes us on our own path
To have met like-minded people
Thank you, youth
Don't throw away your pride, there's nothing to throw away
We can't let it go to waste.
Let's go! Let's go to the future! Let's go to the future!
Come on!
I don't think we should be satisfied
To a world yet to be seen
Draw it, stay free
Still on the road to the end of the journey
That we have found each other
Don't be thankful
Embracing the things that must not change
And keep changing
If we had only been more aggressive, we wouldn't be there yet
Let's be more aggressive with here.
Let's take it easy today.
This is Saori Onoda of Tsubaki Factory
and Nanami Kubota of Ocha-no-Ma, the tea factory, present "Halo! stay!
It's time to say goodbye.
Here's an announcement!
Tsubaki Factory Concert Tour 2023 Autumn will hit!
Riko Yamagishi and Yume Kishimoto's graduation special Akatsuki
DVD and Blu-ray will be released next week!
You can see Riko and Yume's solo songs that I mentioned earlier.
Please check it out!
And Tsubaki Factory Concert Tour 2024 Spring
Come Everybody" will start on May 3!
It will be the last concert with the current group.
We hope everyone will come and see us!
And Ocha-no-Ma Live Tour 2024!
Our hometown is Japan rock band will start on April 7 in Osaka!
Yes, as I said before...
We will do our best to show you a more powerful Ocha-no-Ma.
We are looking forward to seeing you soon!
And on May 1st
Live event in Ocha-no-Ma Lifestyle with Docs 2024
I will perform at Nearly Equal Joy x Ochanoma!
Yes, I'm very nervous.
I will do my best, so please come and join us!
Tsubaki Factory will be performing at Sakofest Universe on April 21!
We are really, really happy to be able to perform.
Please look forward to seeing what kind of music we will be performing!
On May 12, we will be performing with the Halo Pro trainee unit 24.
I will be performing in "Garafis VII Kizuna Fanfare" with the Halo Pro trainee unit 24 on May 12.
We will do our best to show you the current colors of Tsubaki Factory.
And Tsubaki Factory will perform in Shanghai on May 18!
We were really surprised when we got the schedule.
We are so happy to be able to perform overseas again!
We'll do our best to leave our mark on the world.
We will do our best to leave our mark on the world!
Haloste is a channel where the members of Hello Project appear more and more often!
New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
This time we're joined by Saori Onoda of Tsubaki Factory and
and Nanami Kubota from Ochanoma!
Good bye!
Thank you for watching!